{
    "Who is Yasir Khan?": {
        "question": "Who is Yasir Khan?",
        "answer": "A Billionaire",
        "correct": 3,
        "wrong": 1
    },
    "The Brain of computer is called:": {
        "question": "The Brain of computer is called:",
        "answer": "CPU",
        "correct": 4,
        "wrong": 0
    },
    "Who made the first atomic bomb?": {
        "question": "Who made the first atomic bomb?",
        "answer": "Oppenheimer",
        "correct": 3,
        "wrong": 0
    },
    "when did pakistan won World Cup?": {
        "question": "when did pakistan won World Cup?",
        "answer": "1992",
        "correct": 3,
        "wrong": 0
    },
    "Who became the first president of Pakistan?": {
        "question": "Who became the first president of Pakistan?",
        "answer": "Muhammad Ali Jinnah",
        "correct": 2,
        "wrong": 1
    },
    "When did pakistan became a Nuclear power country?": {
        "question": "When did pakistan became a Nuclear power country?",
        "answer": "1998",
        "correct": 3,
        "wrong": 0
    },
    "when did Muslim League established?": {
        "question": "when did Muslim League established?",
        "answer": "1906",
        "correct": 3,
        "wrong": 0
    },
    "which city of Pakistan is most ancient?": {
        "question": "which city of Pakistan is most ancient?",
        "answer": "Multan",
        "correct": 2,
        "wrong": 1
    },
    "who is called the father of computer?": {
        "question": "who is called the father of computer?",
        "answer": "Charles Babbage",
        "correct": 2,
        "wrong": 1
    },
    "Super Computer belongs to which generation?": {
        "question": "Super Computer belongs to which generation?",
        "answer": "fifth",
        "correct": 3,
        "wrong": 0
    },
    "The fastest computer in the world id:": {
        "question": "The fastest computer in the world is:",
        "answer": "Super Computer",
        "correct": 2,
        "wrong": 0
    },
    "why we use loops in our programs?": {
        "question": "why we use loops in our programs?",
        "answer": "For iteration",
        "correct": 1,
        "wrong": 0
    }
}